quiz.questions = [ 
    {
        question: "Which actor portrayed the first live action Superman?",
        answers: {
            a: "George Reeves",
            b: "Christopher Reeve",
            c: "Kirk Alyn"
        },
        correctAnswer: 'c'
    },
    
    {
        question: "Who created the character Spawn?",
        answers: {
            a: "Todd McFarlane",
            b: "Jack Kirby",
            c: "Rob Liefeld"
        },
        correctAnswer: 'a'
    },

    {
        question: "Which Kevin Smith movie is not set in the 'View Askewniverse'?",
        answers: {
            a: "Clerks",
            b: "Mallrats",
            c: "Jersey Girl"
        },
        correctAnswer: 'c'
    },
    
    {
        question: "Who played Daisy Domergue in Quentin Tarantino's 'The Hateful Eight'?",
        answers: {
            a: "Jennifer Love Hewitt",
            b: "Jason Lee",
            c: "Jennifer Jason Leigh"
        },
        correctAnswer: 'c'
    },

    {
        question: "Who wrote the 2004 teen comedy 'Mean Girls?",
        answers: {
            a: "Tina Fey",
            b: "Larry David",
            c: "Emma Thompson"
        },
        correctAnswer: 'a'
    },

    {
        question: "What did Farva want to name his and Ramathorn's car in 'Super Troopers'?",
        answers: {
            a: "Leader Cola",
            b: "Team Ramrod",
            c: "Johnny Chimpo"
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b'
    },

    {
        question: "How much money did Earl win before being hit by a car in 'My Name Is Earl'?",
        answers: {
            a: "$500,000",
            b: "$250,000",
            c: "$100,000"
        },
        correctAnswer: 'c'
    },

    {
        question: "What is the name of Snowman's dog in 'Smokey and the Bandit'?",
        answers: {
            a: "Larry",
            b: "Fred",
            c: "Burt"
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b'
    },

    {
        question: "Which film director is rumoured to have filmed the moon landing?",
        answers: {
            a: "Stanley Kubrick",
            b: "Ingmar Bergman",
            c: "Roman Polanski"
        },
        correctAnswer: 'a'
    },

    {
        question: "Will Smith turned down the role of Neo in 'The Matrix' to make which film?",
        answers: {
            a: "Men In Black 2",
            b: "Wild Wild West",
            c: "Hitch"
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b'
    }
    
    

];

quiz.verdicts = [
    {
        minScore: 100,
        text: " Alright, alright, alright!"
    },
    {
        minScore: 50,
        text: " Pretty, pretty, prettaay good!"
    },
    {
        minScore: 33,
        text: " Think McFly, Think!"
    },
    {
        minScore: 15,
        text: " Fork! Me can't eat soup!"
    },
    {
        minScore: 0,
        text: " Wrong wrong wrong, wrong wrong wrong wrong! You're wrong! you're wrong! YOU'RE WROOONG!!!"
    }
];
